<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PlantFacts</string>

    <string name="aloe_string">Aloe vera is a variety of houseplant that is most known for its medical benefits. It has been grown in tropical climates for many years and cultivated for its medicinal purposes. You can use the healthy compounds of the aloe vera plant to ease scrapes and burns, so it is a great plant to have around the house. This succulent can be found in ointments for burns, skin lotion, drinks and cosmetics. It can also be used for decorative purposes as an indoor plant. This plant has thick, pointed leaves that are usually a green-gray color. The leaves are variegated with spots of white that stretch out directly from the plant’s base.</string>
    <string name="burros_string">Also known as the donkey tail plant, this succulent is one of the easiest plants to propagate and care for, which makes it a popular houseplant. The burro’s tail was given its name because of its ability to grow up to four inches long with a shape that resembles a tail. This species happens to be a cactus and although all cacti are succulents, not all succulents are cacti. This succulent grows best indoors, placed in a well-drained container, where its long stems can drape down off of the edges of the pot.</string>
    <string name="jade_string">The jade plant is similar to a bonsai plant in the way that it grows and is maintained. It has a thick trunk with branches that jut out like a miniature tree. This succulent has thick, shiny, dark green leaves that grow into an oval shape. Some varieties of the jade plant develop a red color at the tip of the leaf. Once the plant matures and if the conditions are right, the jade plant can develop beautiful white or pink flowers that bloom in the shape of a star.</string>
    <string name="snake_string">Native to West Africa, the snake plant is one of the easiest succulents to cultivate. It can be neglected for long periods of time and still maintain its fresh look. This plant has long, variegated leaves in different shades of green. It is one of the most tolerant types of indoor succulents and can survive in rooms with low light and little water. NASA research says this plant can even improve the air quality in your home by removing toxins and pollutants while you sleep!</string>
    <string name="zebra_string">The zebra plant can grow between five and six inches tall and wide. It does not take up a lot of room and does not require much care, so it works well as a houseplant. The zebra plant gets its name from the white variegated stripes on its leaves. These striking leaves point out from its stem in different directions. This plant has shallow roots and is best grown in smaller pots. The zebra plant produces bright yellow, cone-shaped flower heads that last about a week. They are dainty, slow-growing and have an eccentric appearance. They make great gifts and decor for a shelf or desk.</string>

</resources>